The Bible says prophets are sent to utter the deep things of God for the conviction of sin,
for edification and comfort to the people of God.
Prophet T.B. Joshua is used by God to speak words of prophecy into peoples lives, exposing and destroying
the plan of satan against them, in the name of Jesus Christ.
As the man of God was ministering, the power of God fell upon this lady and her deliverance began.
Let's watch what happened next, as the name of Jesus Christ worked in the spirit.
Stand up!
Leave her.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Who are you?
I destroyed her.
She is your daughter?
Yes.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Who are you?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I am her spiritual husband.
I have scattered everything about her.
Go and stand with your daughter.
She does not know anything.
I don’t want her to be great.
I have destroyed her.
[How have you destroyed her?]
She does not know anything.
I have scattered her destiny.
You listen to that?
Destiny has been scattered.
Nothing.
She does not know anything.
She is over; she is finished.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I just want to destroy her because her star is great.
Come on, in the name of Jesus!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come here!
When I count to two - your knee on the floor!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Leave her like that.
Thank You, Jesus!
She is free.
The Holy Spirit casts the demon out and she is given a new heart and desire to follow Jesus Christ.
Her deliverance is complete.
Hallelujah.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Joana Agboga, I am from Edo State but I reside in Abuja.
I'm a student.
I came to thank God for delivering me from the evil spirit that caused me to bedwet,
steal, lie, be angry and very stubborn.
I started bedwetting from when I was small.
When I would bedwet, I'd wake up and feel that the bed was wet and stand up.
Most times, I would cry and tell my mum.
It was every night.
It had been happening on a day to day basis.
As for the stealing, I would go to a supermarket with a huge sum of money
but pick up something worth 50 or 20 naira and leave.
I would not use it.
I would just take it and throw it away; sometimes, I would keep it.
I had the spirit of anger.
I used to get angry at any little thing.
When I got angry, I would bang the door on my mum.
If someone hid money in the house, something would tell me where the money was.
I would go there and get the money no matter where they hid it.
The evil spirit would tell me where the money was and I would steal it.
The lack of knowledge: before exams, I would read but during the exams, everything would black out.
Tell me, what other evil things remain?
Look - what a beautiful girl.
She is bedwetting all the time, she steals...
She can enter the supermarket and steal something.
When she sleeps she bedwetts everywhere, all the time!
She can't travel, she can't go anywhere, she steals...
The bedwetting had affected me in many ways.
I could not go to my sister's house and ask to stay or go to my cousin's house.
I could not go anywhere because of the bedwetting.
I was always not happy, which was not a good thing at all.
This stealing - does it mean that your parents are poor and that is why you steal,
or it was something you could not resist?
Tell us.
My mum and dad gave me whatever I wanted.
I would go to the supermarket with a huge sum of money but pick something worth 10 or 20 naira.
How this thing comes to you?
The voice would direct me to go, that I would not be caught stealing.
There is a voice?
Yes, Sir.
You listen to that.
She said her parents gave her everything, more than what was stolen.
They have enough.
Even if she had 10 000 naira or 5 000 dollars in the pocket
she would still enter the supermarket and steal 1 dollar.
Does it make sense?
Tell your neighbour, "if you fail to realise that there are powers that cause one
to be bowed down in bondage, you will fight the wrong battle."
Now, she has 5 000 but you will see her going to the supermarket and taking 1 dollar.
What does she want to use 1 dollar for - somebody who has 5 000 dollars in the pocket?
What does she want to use it for?
That is to tell you that this is beyond human comprehension.
Ordinarily it is beyond...
There is a force that wants her to be humiliated.
There is a force that wants her to be embarrassed.
There is a force that wants her to be killed.
There is a force that wants her to be imprisoned.
There is a force that wants her to be out of circulation.
If I am talking to you let me see your hand.
There is a force.
You have to stand against it.
Stand up!
Tell your neighbour, "There is a force that wants you to be disgraced.
There is a force that wants you to be condemned.
There is a force that wants you to be imprisoned.
You have to stand against it, in the name of Jesus!
If you fail to realise that there are powers that make people to be humiliated, to be embarrassed,
you will fight a wrong battle."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You may be seated.
There are two ways;
bedwetting to embarrass her among her colleagues, to humiliate her, to make her feel inferior.
She would not be able to talk to colleagues that know she was bedwetting.
I was in a boarding school and I would wet the bed but my classmates would cover up for me.
Every time I urinated, something would wake me that I should stand up.
Then, I would turn over that mattress and leave the room.
I didn’t like watching Emmanuel TV at all.
Whenever Emmanuel TV was on, I was not happy.
I would leave the room.
My mum had to force me to come here today.
You said you bedwetted in the boarding school and your classmates knew about this, didn't you?
Yes, Sir.
What were they saying?
Most of them would say different things; like, in the hostel, I was not able to go to their rooms.
If we were doing something in any of their rooms, I could not sleep over;
I would have to come back to my room.
Most of them would insult me; it was very embarrassing.
Now you say that you did not want to watch Emmanuel TV. Why?
Each time they put Emmanuel TV on, I would leave the room and go and listen to music or watch a movie.
Those who refuse to watch Emmanuel TV in your houses - you should know the reason why.
The sister has revealed - this is a revelation.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Listen, those who don't want to see people healed...
"In the name of Jesus, rise up and walk!" - there are people that do not want to see that kind of things.
Those who do not want to see people being helped, by giving food, charity, assistance, scholarships -
they don't want to see it.
They would say, "This is fake. How can you give this thing? Where did they get the money?
By what authority is this healing of people?"
If I am talking...
Whatever authority...
I'm talking to you - by what authority are you healing people?
I doubt that power.
Me that is talking - what am I using this authority to do?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
She is telling you that she hated watching Emmanuel TV.
This is someone who in the past was bedwetting, stealing, because she didn't want to see
someone being delivered from stealing.
It made her feel irritated.
This is what I am doing - I steal.
If I now watch on TV someone confessing, "I am a thief" and this person would hear, "You are delivered".
And this person would later confirm that the spirit was gone.
Being a thief, I would feel very condemned and worried.
I wouldn't want to watch more, if I am not ready to stop stealing.
If I am talking to you...
I would not be able to sleep that night.
I would continue to think about it.
It is better that I do not hear people talking about stealing, being delivered from stealing,
because I'm there.
Can you see?
Or, I bedwet everyday, but watching Emmanuel TV one would see somebody
being delivered from a spirit of bedwetting.
And I am not ready to come out to say people that I bedwet.
The thing would worry me; I would not be able to sleep.
It would become a burden to my spirit.
It is better for me not to watch such a program.
It is better for me to watch a movie or a program where I would see people proud to be thief, to be this or that.
That would encourage my spirit.
It is better not to watch anything that would not encourage my spirit.
My mum forced me to come to SCOAN.
They forced you to come here?
Yes, sir.
How?
Before she booked the flight, I told my mum that I didn’t want to come.
She told me that I must come.
I said, "Mummy, I don’t want to come".
She said, "You must come".
She forced me.
When we got to the airport, they told us that we had missed the flight
but my mum begged them, that we couldn't miss the flight.
She then paid extra money and we came here.
When we got here for the Saturday service, under the canopy is where my mum was sat.
I left her there and walked around but didn't want to enter the church.
Then, she came inside the main auditorium and I followed her inside.
Prophet T.B. Joshua located me where I had sat down and told me to stand up.
Then, the evil spirit in me started manifesting.
Since my deliverance, I have been free – no spirit telling me to steal, I have not bedwet – nothing.
I sleep and wake up peacefully.
Now, remember that she was not the one I was talking to.
I was talking to the forth person next to her.
Come on, brother.
When I'm talking to this brother, everyone around is being observed.
Everybody around, because Jesus has eyes at the back as good as those in the front.
So, where can you go from His presence?
[Nowhere.]
So, when I located this sister, I was in hurry to leave this brother and go to her.
OK, sit down.
Christianity and religion -
some people don't know the difference between Christianity and religion.
There is a difference.
Religious people are without spirituality
while Christians are born of the Spirit of God.
We are made in our heart to be Christians.
We are only made Christians by living in the Word and by the Word living in us.
Tell your neighbour, “We are made in our heart to be Christians”.
In other words, I mean:
we are only made Christians by living in the Word and by the Word living in us.
Ever since the man of God delivered me, I have been free; I have not bedwetted.
I have not done anything, no evil spirit has told me anything.
I just sleep and wake up peacefully.
I no longer steal or bedwet.
Man of God, I thank you so much for what you have done in my life.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
I am so happy to be here, in your midst today.
My name is Mrs. Elizabeth Agboga, I am from Edo State, I reside in Abuja.
This girl beside me is my daughter.
She had been bedwetting since she was five years old.
When we came from Abuja to The SCOAN, she bedwet in the hotel that we lodged in.
Are you listening to that?
Can you see what a foolish thing?
God has taken it just like that - by His stripes.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Why there would be anyone not recognizing His death on the Calvary?
Just like that.
Tell your neighbour, "You need to be delivered."
Because it is the Spirit of prophet that recognises a prophet.
You cannot recognise things we are talking about.
The greatest miracle that can happen to anyone is when you begin to see what Jesus is looking at,
to go where Jesus wants you to go
and begin to look at yourself... seeing yourself having what Jesus says you have, being able to do things
Jesus says you can do.
That is the greatest miracle.
The contentment we are talking about will come.
You are not content - that is why you are running "helter skelter", no matter the miracle you receive.
Running "helter skelter", living a life of "non-contentment" will rubbish our salvation.
When you are not content there is nothing you cannot do.
It is when you are content...
No matter how little I have - I'm content, it's OK - that is what God wants me to have.
God's time is the best - then you will begin to sleep well,
you will know what to ask for in your prayer,
then you can say, "Thank You, Jesus".
But when you said "Thank You" the last time?
When you pray, you do not remember to say "Thank You".
You only remember an immediate miracle.
All the miracles you have been receiving right from your youth - you have forgotten them.
An immediate miracle.
You are sick now - you forget your good health in the past.
You are poor now - you forget the time when you lived in abundance.
You have a nightmare - you forget the vision you have seen in the past.
Don't wait until you see the light at the end of the tunnel.
Tell your neighbour, “Don't wait to say, 'Thank You' until you see light at the end of the tunnel".
You are inside a tunnel and it is dark - "I will not say 'thank You' unless I get to the end".
Definitely - you will die inside the tunnel.
Those who get to the end of the tunnel are those who say "Thank You, Jesus" right inside the tunnel.
"No matter what I'm going through - thank You, Jesus. No matter what happened - thank You, Jesus.
No matter what is happening to me - thank You, Jesus. I thank You."
They thank before they get to the end of the tunnel.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If I'm talking to you...
While you are inside the tunnel, moving, trying to crawl your body in the dark, you cannot see anything,
say, "Thank You, Jesus".
Don't begin to say, "See me through".
No, there is no word of "Thank you", but "See me through".
Only when you see the light you shout, "Thank You, Jesus - I am going to The SCOAN to give the testimony".
Coming to The SCOAN to give testimony will be delayed.
But if right from the beginning of your journey in the dark you keep saying,
"Thank You, Jesus. I know You will see me through"...
Tell your neighbour, "Thank You, Jesus. I know You will see me through.
Thank You, Jesus. You have seen me through."
Whereas you are not yet at the end of the tunnel, you already say,
"Thank You, Jesus. I know You will see me through.
Thank You, Jesus. You have seen me through.
Thank You, Jesus. I know You will see me through.
Thank You, Jesus. I know You are aware of what I am going through.
Thank You, Jesus. I know You guide me. Thank You, Jesus."
These words of thanking should be more then those of asking, "Heal me".
Tell your neighbour, "The words of thanks should be more than 'Heal me. Deliver me. Set me free.'"
Thank You, Jesus Christ.
If your faith is lifted up let me see your hand.
I was surprised on Sunday.
Since then my daughter has not been bedwetting.
I have been to so many places for deliverance.
Coming to this place, in just one day the bedwetting, stealing and lying stopped.
I was so surprised.
I thank God for everything in my and my children's lives.
On the last day you will stand to witness how you helped your sister to maintain the miracle.
Tell your neighbour, "On the last day, she will stand to testify how she supported her daughter
to maintain the miracle."
Over to you, my hands are cleansed.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You have the right over your daughter to say, "Go to the church. Go to the Bible study. Read the Bible.
Now, you are old enough - go and get married".
The choice you can make, "Go and get married, you stopped to bedwet - go get married."
But it is not the next step now.
The next step for this lady is to have the Word living in her and her living in the Word,
so that she can maintain the miracle.
After that - she can get married, she can do whatever she wants to do.
She has to marry the Word and the Word has to marry her.
Tell your neighbour, “You have to marry the Word and the Word has to marry you.”
Before you get married and settle down,
you must first marry the Word and the Word must marry you.
That is a sound marriage.
These are challenges marriages face today.
Where there is no sound, solid foundation, the marriage crashes.
Marry and re-marry, broken homes everywhere - so many of such in the church today.
You consider everything by age, by status - "I have money. I am a graduate..."
No, first marry the Word and let the Word marry you.
Get married to have a settled home and a solid foundation.
Your wife will understand when the goings are tough or when they are good.
All those things that break homes, cause to scatter, to argue, to divorce - they would understand that all
this would come, and understand what God says about whatever comes to the house - it matters.
If I am talking to you let me see your hand.
You may be seated - thank you.
My advice to parents and the viewers watching is:
they should make sure they know what their children are doing.
Some children don’t like to watch Emmanuel TV, like my own daughter.
You will know that they have an evil spirit in them.
That was the reason she was running away from Emmanuel TV.
In my house, we watch Emmanuel TV, 24 hours a day.
Whenever we watched, my daughter would always run away.
She would go down, play music and watch movies.
No matter what I would say to her, she would refuse to come and watch Emmanuel TV with us.
Before we brought her here, it was very tough for me.
I had been preparing since last year to bring her here -
I would postpone it; one thing or the other caused it not to be possible for me.
This very day, God really helped me and made everything possible for me.
I thank God. Thank You, Jesus!
Thank you - you have listened to that.
My advice to viewers at home is that whatever situation you are in,
if it is similar to my own, please run to Jesus immediately so that God locates you and heal you...
Run to Jesus.
Run to Jesus immediately so that you can be free.
Thank you. Run to Jesus so that you can be free.